<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Magic D8-Ball</string>
    <string name="introText">Welcome to the great dating predictor</string>
    <string name="submitbutton">Submit</string>
    <string name="yesButton">YES</string>
    <string name="noButton">NO</string>
    <string name="responsetextvalue" />
    <string name="blankTextView" />
    <string name="question1" />
    <string name="question2" />
    <string name="question3" />
    <string name="answer3">Enter your answer here</string>
    <string name="answer2">Enter your answer here</string>
    <string name="answer1">Enter your answer here</string>
    <string name="warning">WARNING:</string>
    <string name="intro_welcome">Welcome to the Magic D8-Ball</string>
    <string name="intro_text">
        1) Choose the question you want to answer \n
        2) Type in your answer and hit Submit \n
        3) Wait for the MAGIC \n
    </string>
    <string name="result">
        Based on your answer, \n
        we have determined that.......
    </string>
    <string name="exit_top">
        Leaving the \n
        Magic D8-Ball ?!?
    </string>
    <string name="exit_bottom">
        You\'ll be hearing \n from me soon!
    </string>
    <string name="contentwarning">
        This magic D8-Ball is intended for mature audiences only. Please, if you are easily offended, or do not wish to be subjected to silly
        or potentially crude questions and predictions...\nClose this app now and try Tinder.\n\n
        Thank You,\n
        The Management</string>
    <string name="swipe">&lt; swipe &gt;</string>
    <string name="swipeSplash"> swipe &gt;</string>

    <string-array name="Questions1">
        <item>Which power ranger speaks to you most spiritually?</item>
        <item>What&#8230;is your quest?</item>
        <item>Do you think cats have any regrets?</item>
        <item>What’s the longest you’ve left dropped food on the floor for before picking it up and eating it?</item>
        <item>How many donuts can you fit in your mouth at once?</item>
        <item>Do you like it spicy?</item>
        <item>What is your favourite color?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Questions2">
        <item>How quickly would you leave me for Chris Hemsworth?</item>
        <item>How long are you willing to sit in agony rather than stand up and get an out-of-reach remote?</item>
        <item>How many days do you wear the same pants in a row before it becomes, like, a problem?</item>
        <item>Have you ever been, like, sexually attracted to a piece of fruit?</item>
        <item>Do you think that there is a seperate cat heaven and bird heaven, or do they go to the same one...for the cat’s sake?</item>
        <item>How many seconds into the first movie theatre preview do you finish your bucket of popcorn?</item>
        <item>Backstreet Boys or *NSYNC?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Questions3">
        <item>Which room in Hogwarts would you most want to have sex in?</item>
        <item>How big do you think Thor’s penis is, just like, scientifically speaking?</item>
        <item>Can I trust you to never pressure me into faving one of your tweets? Ever. Like, not even if we get married?</item>
        <item>Nightowl, earlybird, or both?</item>
        <item>Do you think that if two people made out hard enough, they could switch brains?</item>
        <item>Do you put the toilet paper roll on the right way or the wrong way?</item>
        <item>Is butter a carb?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Answers">

        <item>We advise a couple beers to improve the outcome of this date..</item>
        <item>You\'re definitely going to die alone.</item>
        <item>They tell me they can\'t wait for your date.</item>
        <item>On second thought, bring flowers too.</item>
        <item>Listen it’s not my fault your father didn\'t love you. Get off my back!</item>
        <item>Ask again later. I can\'t…I just can\'t deal with this right now.</item>
        <item>You weren\'t born smart, but it looks like a change is in the air&#8230;good luck!</item>
        <item>You should tell your date to FUCK OFF!</item>
        <item>Stay home and drink heavily!</item>
        <item>How do you feel about livestock for an alternative dating experience?</item>
        <item>No one likes you!! I\'m sure you knew that&#8230;</item>
        <item>Pack a bag full of condoms and head out!</item>
        <item>Invest money in a match maker!</item>
        <item>You can leave the antibiotics at home.</item>
        <item>You will live a long happy life together&#8230; so you think.</item>
        <item>Save time, stop looking, you have found your match.</item>
        <item>You rely on the magic 8-ball too much! Get a life!</item>
        <item>You will never be lonely again!</item>
        <item>Tonight will be the best tossed salad you ever had.</item>
        <item>Use birth control!</item>
        <item>You will get laid tonight if you play your cards right!</item>
        <item>Don\'t expect love&#8230;or your date, to show up.</item>
        <item>Don\'t fret my pet, all will be well&#8230;</item>
        <item>It\'s not just your mom who likes you, so does your upcoming date.</item>
        <item>Don\'t just give up&#8230;you\'re not hopeless or ugly!</item>
        <item>Buy some eggs before your date&#8230;you\'ll be making breakfast in bed.</item>
        <item>Just nod your head, smile and bring lube.</item>
        <item>I see warts in your future!</item>
        <item>Tomorrow, invest heavily in antibiotics.</item>
        <item>Hope you\'ve been practicing cardio for your 17 seconds in heaven!</item>
        <item>You will disappear, and no one will find the body.</item>
        <item>Huuuuuuuuuummmmmmmmmm!!!!!!!</item>
        <item>Smile and stop thinking of your ex. I predict good times ahead.</item>
        <item>WTF!</item>
        <item>WTF! (Wrestle Then Fuck)</item>
        <item>I don\'t like you enough to give you a prediction&#8230;</item>
        <item>I predict you will shake the 8-ball again&#8230;</item>
        <item>Your date is a stalker&#8230;BONUS?</item>
        <item>You will be in love for one night&#8230;</item>
        <item>Put down the pipe&#8230;be alert&#8230;don\'t mess this up!</item>
        <item>RUN!</item>
        <item>I see a Viagra refill in the future.</item>
        <item>Your date will beat you silly tonight&#8230;in a good way&#8230;score!!!!!</item>
        <item>For a good time call &#8230;someone who gives a fuck!</item>
        <item>You have a better chance having sex with your pillow!</item>
        <item>Don\'t commit suicide with a butter knife yet, hot night ahead!</item>
        <item>You will turn into a dildo at midnight!</item>
        <item>You will be married in Vegas by the end of the night.</item>
        <item>Yes&#8230; you will fall in love tonight&#8230;but will they?!?</item>
        <item>Giggity, Giggity!!!</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
